[{"answer": "You know, it's obviously, a death toll, it's smaller and we don't know an official death toll, numbers vary and nobody really knows if -- there is no actual search for those who have died.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "How does this compared being on the ground where you are right now in Tacloban to what you've covered before?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, I'm here with Paula Hancocks.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Are you getting a feeling that people are just getting very desperate of bordering on anarchy?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What are you going to say?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Piers, that's one of the things I don't understand is that I was just -- the make-shift clinic here at the airport and Paula has been there as well.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "So it's actually survive the storm surge, the typhoon, and then to seriously question whether you can survive the airports?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, this is very much the staging ground of the disaster relief operation.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Anna, what are you seeing down there?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, the basics do apply here, Piers, there's no question and all of the things we're hearing from Paula and Anderson and Anna there.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What are the immediate problems now that will be facing rescuers on the ground?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Basically the guidelines have been loosened for who can get these statin drugs.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "How it will change things for Americans?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "I mean you know, you're trying to make Americans fitter, faster, leaner, eat healthier, exercise and so on and now they can think actually there's a much easier way just pop a few pills?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think there's no two ways about that.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "This is turning into a huge mess, isn't it?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, I think eventually many of the glitches will get fixed and indeed more people will be covered but the problem that that whole Affordable Care Act has is it doesn't incorporate all the innovations.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "If it all worked well it would be a force of good in America?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "You know, as the leader, as his best friend on the team, that's what has me miffed, how I miss this and I never saw it.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "You're telling me that wasn't any signs going into that?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, you have a public access cable TV show, I could tell you fully but I can't on your show.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Were you getting a sense of bullying or are you getting a sense of pretty regular dressing room banter?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I think the great thing about being in sports is that you don't have to grow up.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Is it really that surprising that they whip themselves up in this way and have such extremely competitive banter if you like?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "I think (inaudible) because I don't want to bang into the metal thing.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "His head just went, where do we go?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "ANGE: Yeah, well, it's brilliant comic at work, Piers.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "You were laughing there watching yourself passing out?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, the times you were there I might have been going through hell because I was on for eight and half years.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "How many people did know the real depths of what you're going through?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, listen, I was not of a straight mind.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "What was going through your mind that day?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I still do.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "... did you feel a terrible sense of guilt about what you've put her through?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "My fingers on the pulse of pop culture.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Well, how right were you Artie Lange?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "That is -- listen Conan's been so good to me over the years, man.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What is extraordinary is you can't even remember appearing that time right?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Oh God, yes.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Where you had this huge audience that was your family and explained as you are to me now?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I think I would call us friends -- friendly.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "You're still friends?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, listen I know a lot crooked Jersey contractors into painting your house, that's about the price.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Francis Bacon's painting of his fellow artist Lucian Freud $142 million, are we on the wrong game?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "We like to sing in church, we like to sing, \"Take Me Out to the Ball Game\" together.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "I mean it would take them about two minutes right?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Oh just amazing people in media and...", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Who else have you got, big name?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It's pure Presidential poetry but the biggest thing is that it's doubling down on our original promise, made by Thomas Jefferson.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "What makes the Gettysburg Address in your opinion, the greatest American Speech?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Well, you know, when you have discussions about Baseball or Rock Music you will have to say besides Bay Ruth and the Beatles, here you have to say besides Washington.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "If you could put one back in power now you'd put them back in power?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I think JFK is an unfinished story.", "docId": "131112pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "What about JFK?", "qSentId": 564}]